<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Freelancing Course</string>
    <string name="banner_adUnit" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-5838182687945471/6889251449</string>
    <!-- Sample Banner AdUnit ID: ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/9214589741 -->
    <!-- Production Banner AdUnit ID: ca-app-pub-5838182687945471/6889251449 -->
    <string name="adMob_Id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-5838182687945471~7074682768</string>
    <!-- sample id: ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713 -->
    <!-- production id: ca-app-pub-5838182687945471~7074682768 -->
    <string name="support">Support Us for more FREE Content!</string>
    <string name="firstIconText">1. What is Freelancing?</string>
    <string name="secondIconText">2. Freelancing Platforms</string>
    <string name="thirdIconText">3. How to Start Freelancing</string>
    <string name="fourthIconText">4. How to create Fiverr Account</string>
    <string name="fifthIconText">5. Earn Money by Writing Content</string>
    <string name="sixthIconText">6. Earn Money by Logo Designing</string>
    <string name="firstIconDesc" translatable="false">An icon showing a person sitting on couch with laptop</string>
    <string name="secondIconDesc" translatable="false">An icon showing a person trying to figure out his path</string>
    <string name="thirdIconDesc" translatable="false">a person with laptop</string>
    <string name="fourthIconDesc" translatable="false">a person trying to create account on fiverr</string>
    <string name="fifthIconDesc" translatable="false">a person designing logo on computer</string>
    <string name="sixthIconDesc" translatable="false">a person editing videos on computer</string>
    <string name="bottomIcon1Desc" translatable="false">A light bulb on top of some books</string>
    <string name="Article1_Intro">Freelancing means earning money online with help of your skills. Freelancing has become a popular career choice in Pakistan over the past few years. With the rise of online platforms and the increasing demand for remote work, freelancing has opened up new opportunities for professionals in Pakistan. If you are looking to start freelancing in Pakistan, there are a few things you need to know. In this article, we will guide you through the process of starting your freelancing career in Pakistan and provide you with some tips to help you succeed.</string>
    <string name="Article1_heading1">1. Choose your Niche:</string>
    <string name="Article1_Para1">The first step to becoming a successful freelancer is to choose your niche. A niche is a specific area of expertise in which you specialize. You need to determine what you are good at and what services you can offer to clients. In Pakistan, popular freelancing niches include graphic design, web development, content writing, digital marketing, and data entry.</string>
    <string name="Article1_heading2">2. Build Your Portfolio:</string>
    <string name="Article1_Para2">Once you have chosen your niche, the next step is to build your portfolio. Your portfolio is a collection of your best work that showcases your skills and expertise. It is essential to have a strong portfolio that demonstrates your abilities to potential clients. You can create a portfolio website or use platforms like Behance, Dribbble, or LinkedIn to showcase your work.</string>
    <string name="Article1_heading3">3. Choose the Right Platform:</string>
    <string name="Article1_Para3">There are several freelancing platforms available in Pakistan that you can use to find work. Some of the popular platforms include Upwork, Fiverr, Freelancer, and PeoplePerHour. You need to choose the right platform that matches your skills and expertise. Each platform has its own set of rules, fees, and requirements. It is essential to read the terms and conditions of each platform before you start working.</string>
    <string name="Article1_heading4">4. Set Your Rates:</string>
    <string name="Article1_Para4">Setting your rates is a crucial step in starting your freelancing career. You need to determine your hourly or project-based rates based on your skills, experience, and niche. In Pakistan, the average hourly rate for freelancers is between $10 to $30 per hour. However, it is essential to research the market and set competitive rates that reflect your expertise.</string>
    <string name="Article1_heading5">5. Create a Strong Profile:</string>
    <string name="Article1_Para5">Your profile is the first thing that clients see when they visit your freelancing platform. You need to create a strong profile that showcases your skills, expertise, and experience. Your profile should include a professional profile picture, a catchy headline, and a well-written bio. You should also include your portfolio, your rates, and your work history.</string>
    <string name="Article1_heading6">6. Start Applying for Work:</string>
    <string name="Article1_Para6">Once you have set up your profile, the next step is to apply for jobs. You can search for jobs based on your niche, skills, and location. It is essential to read the job description carefully and tailor your proposal to the client\'s needs. You should also include your portfolio, your rates, and your relevant experience in your proposal.</string>
    <string name="Article1_heading7">7. Create a Good Work Relationship:</string>
    <string name="Article1_Para7">Building relationships with clients is essential to succeed as a freelancer. You need to provide high-quality work, meet deadlines, and communicate effectively with clients. You should also ask for feedback and reviews from clients to improve your skills and reputation. Building long-term relationships with clients can lead to repeat work and referrals.</string>
    <string name="conclusion">Conclusion:</string>
    <string name="Article1_conclusion">Freelancing can be a rewarding career choice for professionals in Pakistan. By following these steps, you can start your freelancing career and succeed in the online marketplace. Remember to choose your niche, build your portfolio, choose the right platform, set your rates, create a strong profile, apply for jobs, and build relationships with clients. Good luck with your freelancing career!</string>
    <string name="Article2_Intro">In today\'s digital age, freelancing has become an increasingly popular option for individuals looking for flexible work arrangements and for companies looking for a cost-effective solution to their staffing needs. Pakistan, in particular, has seen an increase in the number of freelancers in recent years, thanks to the availability of reliable internet connectivity and a growing pool of talented professionals. To meet this growing demand, a number of freelancing platforms have emerged in Pakistan, providing an easy and user-friendly way for job seekers and employers to connect with each other. In this article, we will take a closer look at some of the most popular freelancing platforms available in Pakistan, their features, and how they can help you achieve your career goals.</string>
    <string name="Article2_heading1" translatable="false">1. Upwork</string>
    <string name="Article2_Para1">Upwork is one of the most popular freelancing platforms globally, and has a significant presence in Pakistan. The platform boasts over 12 million freelancers and over 5 million registered clients. Upwork offers a wide range of job categories, including web development, graphic design, writing, and customer service, among others. The platform allows freelancers to create a profile that showcases their skills and experience, as well as bid on projects posted by clients. Upwork charges a service fee based on the freelancer\'s earnings, with rates ranging from 5 to 20 depending on the size of the project.</string>
    <string name="Article2_heading2" translatable="false">2. Freelancer</string>
    <string name="Article2_Para2">Freelancer is another popular freelancing platform in Pakistan that offers a range of jobs including software development, data entry, and writing. Freelancer has more than 50 million registered users and has facilitated more than 18 million projects since its inception. Like Upwork, Freelancer allows freelancers to create a profile and bid on projects posted by clients. Freelancer charges a service fee of 10 or $5, whichever is greater, on all projects. The platform also offers a number of tools and resources to help freelancers improve their skills and increase their chances of winning projects.</string>
    <string name="Article2_heading3" translatable="false">3. Fiverr</string>
    <string name="Article2_Para3">Fiverr is a unique freelancing platform that focuses on micro jobs or gigs. Freelancers on Fiverr offer services starting at $5 and can go up to $10,000 per project. Fiverr has more than 5.5 million registered clients and more than 830,000 freelancers offering services in more than 300 categories. On Fiverr, freelancers create a profile and list their services, which clients can browse and buy directly. Fiverr charges a service fee of 20 on all transactions, with additional fees for optional features such as expedited shipping or a priority list.</string>
    <string name="Article2_heading4" translatable="false">4. Guru</string>
    <string name="Article2_Para4">Guru is a freelancing platform that offers a range of job categories including web development, design and writing. The platform has over 3 million registered freelancers and over 1.5 million clients. Guru allows freelancers to create profiles and bid on projects posted by clients. The platform charges a service fee of 5 on all transactions, with no additional fees for membership or bidding fees. Guru also offers a number of tools and resources to help freelancers grow their business, including project management and invoicing software.</string>
    <string name="Article2_heading5" translatable="false">5. PeoplePerHour</string>
    <string name="Article2_Para5">PeoplePerHour is a UK-based freelancing platform with a significant presence in Pakistan. The platform offers several job categories including web development, graphic design, and content writing. Freelancers on PeoplePerHour create a profile and can apply to projects posted by clients, or clients can invite freelancers to submit proposals. PeoplePerHour charges a 20 service fee on all transactions up to £175, with a lower fee for higher value projects.</string>
    <string name="Article2_conclusion">Whether you are a freelancer looking for work or an employer looking for talent, there are many freelancing platforms available in Pakistan to choose from. Each platform offers its own unique set of features and benefits, so it\'s important to choose the one that best suits your needs. When choosing a freelancing platform, it is important to consider factors such as the types of jobs available, the size of the platform\'s user base, the platform\'s fee structure, and the quality of support and resources available to freelancers. It\'s also important to remember that freelancing is a competitive field, and success requires a combination of talent, hard work, and dedication. Whether you\'re a seasoned freelancer or just starting out, it\'s important to constantly improve your skills and market yourself effectively to stand out from the competition. By choosing the right freelancing platform and constantly improving your skills, you can succeed as a freelancer and take advantage of the many opportunities available in Pakistan\'s growing digital economy.</string>
    <string name="switch_en" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="switch_ur" translatable="false">اردو</string>
    <string name="Article3_Intro">Freelancing is very simple just you need one laptop, an internet connection, and a personal mobile. You can easily start freelancing in Pakistan. This question is very popular on search engines how to start freelancing you may also find many videos on this topic. You just need hard work and learning skills to make the best out of freelancing. To understand this topic better I have mentioned below the top 10 skills for freelancing. These skills are high-paid and trending on the top freelancing platforms including Fiverr, Upwork, Guru, etc.</string>
    <string name="Article3_heading1">Top 10 Skills For Freelancing</string>
    <string name="Article3_Para1" translatable="false"><ul><li>Content Writing</li>\n<li>Logo Designing</li>\n<li>Image Background Remover.</li>\n<li>Facebook Ads Manager.</li>\n<li>Video Editing</li>\n<li>Tiktok Video Editor.</li>\n<li>Amazon Virtual Assistant.</li>\n<li>Typing Jobs.</li>\n<li>Article to Video Converter.</li>\n<li>Presentation Designer</li></ul></string>
    <string name="Article3_Para2">So let’s start… step by step, beginners to advanced level guide. Learning Freelancing in very easy steps.</string>
    <string name="Article3_heading2">First Step: Follow the best Youtube Channels for learning skills for FREE</string>
    <string name="Article3_Para3">As we said earlier, there are many channels on youtube that teach skills for free, you do not need to buy any courses or pay a single penny to anyone. This is the first step toward your freelancing journey. There are many youtubers such as Amir Iqbal, Hisham Sarwar, Enablers, and our own Youtube channel Geeky Academy. You can get Fiverr Tutorial from beginners to advanced level on our channel all step-by-step for free.</string>
    <string name="Article3_heading3">Second Step: Explore the Freelancing Skills thats best for You!</string>
    <string name="Article3_Para4">The biggest mistake that most of the new freelancers make is that they just follow the trend, they see whatever is hot-topic right now they start following it, just as it is the case with Amazon, Ecommerce, Drop Shipping etc. No doubt that Amazon and all these online businesses are really great, they are life-changing but not everything is for everyone.</string>
    <string name="Article3_Para5">Do you think we could have gotten great players like Messi, Ronaldo or World Record Runner like Usain Bolt if those guys had not explored different things? Had they stayed stuck at school or had they never thought that I am good at football or I want to be the fastest runner, we would have lost such diamonds.</string>
    <string name="Article3_Para6">Therfore, it is very important to explore different skills before you make up your mind about which skill suits you which type of freelancing excites you. Be it Ecommerce, Digital Marketing, Content Writing, Search Engine Optimization, or Web Development. The key takeaway is to explore these skills, take short free courses such as from DigiSkills or watch Youtube videos.</string>
    <string name="Article3_heading4">Third Step: Start Doing! (Doers are Succeeders)</string>
    <string name="Article3_Para7">After you have finally found what you are good at or what freelancing skill suits you, You must start practicing it and make up your mind that YOU HAVE TO DO IT! You have to master that one skill and that is the secret to succeed. Start Building your portfolio, do some free projects or charge minimum free in the beginning so that you can start creating your portfolio. After putting a decent amount of work you will soon have something to show to your future clients.</string>
    <string name="Article3_Para8">Now, you can fill up your profiles on Fiverr, Upwork or any Freelancing platform with this portfolio of work you have done. It will definitely give you a big advantage over the people who start fresh and do not have anything in their freelancer profile to show as portfolio. This is one secret that leads to getting your first order on these freelancing platforms. Good Luck!</string>
    <string name="Article3_conclusion">Starting freelancing is not as difficult as it seem, it takes only three steps: Watch, Learn, Do it!. All you have to do it learn skills for free from Youtube and other resources, then put those skills to practice by working on free projects or with minimum price, then when you have a decent portfolio built up, start providing your services on the giant freelancing platforms. Don\'t Forget to subscribe our channel on Youtube as Geeky Academy and leave a good review for this app on PlayStore.</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">More Lessons Coming Soon in Next Update, Stay Tuned..</string>
    <string name="Article4_Intro">Creating an account on Fiverr is not a difficult task just follow the step-by-step guidelines. Your Fiverr account will be created within a few minutes. I have divided the complete process into a few steps that will help you to understand easily as a beginner. Especially, this post-corona time in the world, students are searching for a job to work online to manage their educational expenses.</string>
    <string name="Article4_heading1">HOW TO CREATE A FIVERR ACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="Article4_para1">Just Following the step below, you will be able to create your account very easily. Also, check the Fiverr tutorial tips mentioned below that will help you to avoid mistakes that most new sellers on Fiverr do. Let’s start.</string>
    <string name="Article4_heading2">STEP NO 1: CREATE A NEW GMAIL ACCOUNT FOR FIVERR</string>
    <string name="Article4_para2">First, you have to create your new personal Gmail id for Fiverr account use. If you have old Gmail then well done. You do not have to create a new account or if you do not have an id and want to create a new id only for using Fiverr then, First of all, create a new Gmail account.</string>
    <string name="Article4_heading3">STEP NO 2: OPEN FIVERR BEST FREELANCING WEBSITE</string>
    <string name="Article4_para3">First, open your Google Chrome browser and type in the search bar “fiverr.com” and press enter. You will see the World Best Freelancing Website Home page appear on your laptop screen. Then click on the Join button at the top right corner.</string>
    <string name="Article4_heading4">STEP NO 3: CLICK THE JOIN BUTTON ON FIVERR</string>
    <string name="Article4_para4">After clicking on the join Button on the Fiverr website a new pop-up window will appear. You just have to fill-in with your personal active email address. This is very important to use active email you will get future notifications on your email account.</string>
    <string name="Article4_heading5">STEP NO 4: CHOOSE A UNIQUE USER NAME FOR FIVERR</string>
    <string name="Article4_para5">Now choose a unique user name and create a strong password and click on “JOIN” Your Fiverr username must be 8 to 15 characters long and do not use special characters. Try to create a user name related to your real name like “SameerShaikh, SalmaKhan, AayaanRajput.” This is very important to become a brand on Fiverr and easy to remember for clients who will contact you again.</string>
    <string name="Article4_heading6">STEP NO 5: LAST BUT NOT LEAST “ACTIVATE YOUR ACCOUNT”</string>
    <string name="Article4_para6">After choosing a username that is available on Fiverr with a strong password then at last click on the “JOIN” button. Now Fiverr will send you a confirmation email on your email address that is given above. Then open your Gmail account and click on Fiverr email then click “Activate Your Account.”</string>
    <string name="Article4_para7">Congratulation, your account is now created successfully. Now you are the part of Best Freelancing website, Fiverr. you have the opportunity to work online with worldwide clients. Just staying at home anywhere in the world, you can connect with international clients and deliver your service easily on Fiverr. It doesn’t matter where you are living, you have a big home or office. Every client just focuses on your Fiverr profile, positive feedback and your previous work experience then gives you order on Fiverr.</string>
    <string name="Article5_Intro">In this lesson, we will discuss How to become a content writer on Fiverr and make money online as a content writer. To become an article writer on what you need, to make money online step-by-step. We will also share some tips to become an article writer on Fiverr. Many freelancers make mistakes as a beginner content writers on Fiverr and as a result they do not get orders on Fiverr. For example, if you want to become a content writer then first identify your expertise in which article writing category you are an expert. It is not possible for a content writer to write content in all categories. If you have expertise in writing articles on Technology topics then you may not have any idea how to write an article on health topics. Both Health and Technology content writing categories need different knowledge to write SEO-friendly articles.</string>
    <string name="Article5_heading1">What is Content Writing on Fiverr?</string>
    <string name="Article5_Para1">Content writing is the most powerful skill to communicate with readers through words, letters, or sentences. In simple words, content writing on Fiverr is a digital skill that can be used to earn money online on Fiverr. It includes different services like Article and blog post writing, Resume writing, book and e-book writing, Podcast writing, creative writing, etc. It is the most in-demand niche on Fiverr to earn money online. If you want to become an expert content writer on Fiverr then become an expert in following low competition content writing gigs on Fiverr.</string>
    <string name="Article5_heading2">Low-Competition Niches on Fiverr for Content Writing.</string>
    <string name="Article5_Para2" translatable="false"><ul><li>Product Description Writing (only 28,506 services available)</li>\n<li>Ghost book writer ( only 7106 services available)</li>\n<li>Creative writing ( only 4683 services available)</li>\n<li>Speech writing (only 1118 services available)</li>\n<li>Affiliate article writing (only 2505 services available)</li></ul>></string>
    <string name="Article5_heading3">Is Fiverr Good for Content Writing?</string>
    <string name="Article5_Para3">Yes, Fiverr is the best option for content writers to make money online while staying at home. Fiverr has international clients that hire content writers for their blog. Here clients demand quality of work within the required time duration. If you are talented, energetic, and creative content writing skills then Fiverr is the best choice for you to make money online without investment.</string>
    <string name="Article5_heading4">What Skills are Required for a Content Writer?</string>
    <string name="Article5_Para4">Content writer must be an expert in the English language having rich vocabulary and sentences. You must have good research skills related to your content writing category. Your content must be SEO-friendly and knowledgeable for readers. Always try to deliver your experience and knowledge to the readers in simple words.</string>
    <string name="Article5_heading5">How Can I Earn Money From Content Writing?</string>
    <string name="Article5_Para5">There are very talented Freelancers working online from their home, and earning money. Content writing is a unique skill to share your ideas and emotions using words and sentences with your readers. Do you know many Professional Freelancers charging $1000 dollar for just 850 words articles? Yes, the Top Rated sellers on Fiverr charge $1000 dollars for just 850 words because they have a good wealth of experience, portfolio, and they have expertise in their specific category. As a beginner content writer, you have a good opportunity to take advantage of their high price and offer your services at a lower rate so that people who can not afford to pay $1000 for just 850 words, they will come to you to buy your services and place orders, this way you will earn money from content writing just Join Fiverr now and start freelancing. There, you have thousands of opportunities to earn money online from content writing. Just Join on Fiverr Free.</string>
    <string name="Article5_conclusion">Fiverr is the Best Website to earn money online as a Content writer. Here you can sell your content writing gigs at a minimum of $5 to a maximum of $1000 dollar for 850 words of content. This price depends on your content writing skills and years of experience and previous portfolio. Create an account on Fiverr step-by-step by following the guidelines in this app and explore more skills that you can learn to make money on fiverr. Do not forget to rate this app and leave an honest review on Playstore.</string>

</resources>